Usage specs are not checked in to my git
repository. So when I pull down a
project from scratch, I need to make
sure I reinstall my usage specs so that
I can continue developing effectively.
I'll show this being done alongside the
usual npm install ritual purely because
it's a comparable process.
I have all the information in my package
JSON and tessle JSON to pull down both
my application dependencies and usage
specs respectively. Like my node modules
folder, I don't add my actual usage
specs into my git repository. So I need
to reinstall both before my project is
set up.
I'll do this from my terminal, but I
could also ask my agent. I'll run npm
install to download my library
dependencies followed by tessle registry
install to download my usage specs.
Now we can see we have a node modules
folder containing my dependencies as
well as a usage specs folder under the
tzle directory holding all my usage
specs.
You've now reinstalled all the usage
specs and are ready for further
development.